Keith Black

Phone: (845) 625-9783 | Email: Keithblack4290@gmail.com | Denver, Colorado 80231 LinkedIn: /kblack4290 | Portfolio: kblack4290.github.com | GitHub:/kblack4290

Objective

Hard-working individual with proficiency in HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, as well as ability to communicate effectively in a team setting, and possessing a strong willingness to learn from an experienced team as a Junior Web Developer.

Technical Skills

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Postman, Insomnia

Tools: Node, Query, Bootstrap, Foundation, Handlebars, Express, Heroku

Projects

Haggle | github.com/domrafiti/ProjectTwoHaggle | haggle-proj.herokuapp.com/

• Summary: A bartering and trading application

• Role: Html, CSS, and assisted JavaScript

• Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Foundation, API's

Concoctions | github.com/glchavez/Project-One | glchavez.github.io/Project-One/

- Summary: An application that provides recipes
- Role: Html, CSS, and assisted JavaScript
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Foundation, API's

Taker of Notes | https://github.com/Kblack4290/Taker-Of-Notes | the-taker-of-notes.herokuapp.com/

- Summary: An application where the user can take and reference notes
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express, Node

Education and Certification

Full Stack Flex Course December 2020-June 2021 University of Denver (https://bootcamp.du.edu/coding/) Trilogy Education Services Denver, Colorado

Bachelor of Science December 2013

Major: History Minor: Business Administration State University of New York at Plattsburgh

Plattsburgh, New York

Experience

Robert Half/Shane Co., Denver, Colorado February 2021 - Present

OA Data Analyst

- Performed testing in DEV, QA and Pre-Production environment.
- Experienced in manual testing, website quality, and hotfixes.
- Developed, executed, and updated functional and regression test suites.
- Worked with QA manager to accurately assess defect severity and priority.
- Used applications like Browser Stack to ensure the website was functional on a variety of devices and browsers.
- Reported and recorded detailed information about all issues experienced throughout testing.
- Performed Peer review for every regression test suits.
- Worked on SAP (CRM & ECC), Executed queries to manage the ERP system.
- Coordinated with external testing teams to provide proper feedback procedures as well as guidelines for issues

clarity and accuracy.

- Executed System Testing by linking customer from Hybris to CSC application.
- Evaluated issues that users encounter during user acceptance testing to determine impact.
- Worked as a production support team member and resolved the production issues.

Cornerstone Apartment Services, Denver, Colorado October 2017 – December 2020 *Portfolio Manager*

- Managed 335 Apartments in various properties from small multi-family homes to large apartment buildings totaling over \$50,000,000 in assets.
- Managed a team of maintenance technicians and oversee completed maintenance work to ensure the quality and service to residents.
- Serviced and prioritize resident's maintenance requests.
- Conducted negotiations and create relationships with third party vendors.
- Maintained quality resident relations and customer service.
- Implemented resident retention strategies.
- Weekly meetings with leasing to brainstorm, organize, and implement leasing strategies.
- Meet with investors and clients to review property goals and improvements.
- Effectively reduce delinquency to increase NOI.
- Optimized rental income and improve curb appeal.
- Developed and oversee the budget and financial reports to maximize profitability.
- Consistently reach monthly budget and collection goals.
- Maintained monthly budget and prepare bonus summaries, month end reports and leasing summaries.
- Oversaw and control Capital Expenditure Projects to meet or exceed budget expectations.

eBay, Beacon, New York April 2016 - January 2020

Online Retailer

- Created, marketed, and managed successful online retail business with over \$3,000 per month in sales.
- Responsible for all bookkeeping, shipping, public relations, purchasing and quality assurance.
- Promoted business through social media sites, Facebook, and Pinterest.
- Efficiently managed inventory of over 500 items with constant flow of units into and out of the storage area.
- Able to satisfy multiple client orders and maintain excellent feedback rating of over 99%.

Areas of Strength

Communication • Adaptability • Problem Resolution Critical Thinking • Creativity • Customer Service • Learning Agility • Analytical Abilities • Dependability • Client and Customer Retention • Leadership

Computer Skills

Microsoft Office – Excel, Outlook, Word, PowerPoint and Publisher • Google Suite – Gmail, Drive, Docs, Sheets and Meet • VS Code • GitHub • GitLab • Git Bash • Postman • Insomnia • Node • Express • MySQL • MongoDB • Bootstrap • JavaScript • JQuery • API • CSS • HTML • DocuSign • SAP • CSC • JIRA • Adobe • Yardi • OneSite

References available upon request.